Yagoda, Louis Arbitration files 5802
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Louis Yagoda Arbitration files
1961-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Yagoda, Louis
5802
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5710636
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial.; Arbitration and award.; Yagoda, Louis
5710636
- 1961 A-L ---- 1964. (Box 1)
  - 1991-A-L, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1961-m-2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1962-A-L (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1963-A-L (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1962-M-Z, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1963-M-Z (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1964 Awards, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1965 A-M ---- 1969(b). (Box 2)
  - Awards- A-M- 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Awards- N-2 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Awards A-M 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Awards- N-Z- 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1967 Awards H-Z (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1968 Awards A Thru G (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1968 Awards H Thru W (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - A Thru G 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - H Thru Y 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 1970 A-W ---- 1974. (Box 3)
  - 1970 Awards A-W (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1971 Awards 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Awards 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1974 Awards (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 1975 A-J ---- 1977 N-Y. (Box 4)
  - 1975 Awards A Thru J, 1971-1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1975 Award K Thru, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1976 Awards, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Awards- 1977 A-M (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1977 N-Y (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 1978 ---- 1982. (Box 5)
  - 1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1980 Awards (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1981 Awards (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Scope and Contents
    Voluntary Labor Arbitration Tribunal
- 1983 ---- Public Law Board #1264. (Box 6)
  - 1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1984 Awards (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1985 Awards (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 356 Chicago NW. UTU (9), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Completed Awards 1 Thru 87 Incl., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Completed Awards 95- also includes #124 + #297 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - PLB #550, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Denver PLB- 66 th Completed, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Public Law Board No. 731 Penn Central transp. Co. (New Haven Div.) & U.T.U. (T), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Completed PLB 841, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - PLB #1026- Penn Central Transp. Co. and Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - PLB#1124 Western Maryland Railway Co. & United Transportation Union (T), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - PLB # 1165 NorFolk + Western Rail C, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Public Law Board # 1264 New Haven RR Branch of Penn Central Transp. Co., 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Public Law Board (PLB) 844. National Railroad Adjustment Board. 1970. (Box 7)
  - PVB 12vg, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - PLB 844, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - PLB#1351 River Terminal Railway Co., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - P.L.B Board No. 1427, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - PLB No. 1428 Norfolk & Western R, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - P.L.B Board No. 1488 The Lake Terminal RR Co. & UTU, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - PLB NO. 1489 Burlington Northern, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - PLB NO. 1538 Norfolk & Western RR Co UTU (T), 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - PLB NO.1583 Norfolk And Western RR CO. United Transportation Union, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - PLB 1658 - Cleveland, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - PLB # Norfolk and Western Railway Co. & UTU (T), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - PLB # 1717 So. Buffalo R.R. & United Transportation Union, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - PLB NO. 17118 MONONGAHAWA- TWVA Pittsburgh, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - PLB # 1727- Great Lakes & River Dist. - Central RR Company of New Jersey, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - PLB # 1751 Norfolk and Western Railway Co. United Trans. Union, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - PLB #1826 Aliquippa & Southern & Transport Workers of America, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - PLB # 1829 Monongahela Connecting RR. Co. & United Transportation Union, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - PLB # 1842 Former Penn Central of N.J. & UTU (T), 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - PLB NO. 1889 Patapsco & Back Rivers RR And United Transportation Union, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - PLB NO. 1983- Missouri Pacific RR & Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - PLB 1912- Aliquippa & Southern RR & Transport Workers Union Of America Pittsburgh, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - PLB # 1923 Norfolk & Western Railway Co. United Transportation Union (T), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - PLB # 1964- Conrail & UTU, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - PLB # 2097 Detroit, Toledo & Ironton RR Co. & UTU Dearborn, Mich., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - PLB 2162 Peoria & Pekin Union Railway Co. & Brasc (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - PLB 2163 Consolidated Rail Corp & UTU, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - PLB 2221- Former Penn Central Trans Co- BLE, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - PLB NO. 2427 Burlington Northern/ UTU St. Paul Minnesota, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - PLB 2436 BRAC/National Passenger Corp. Washington. D.C., 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - PLB 2613 Conrail/ BM & BK Philadelphia, Pa, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - NRAB Dockets, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - N.R.A.B. July 31, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Public Law Board, Type and Release, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 2409, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Award No. 2 -39
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board 1964 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - National Railraod Adjustment Board Chicago, ILL. (Bird Div.), 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Misc., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Labor Arbitration Awards General Electric Company, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Dumont (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Engelhard Minerals & Chemicals Corp.and Local 1668, U.A.W. Carteret, N.J., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Sub- Contracting + Plant Removal, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Discharge and Discipline (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Arbitration - N.L.R.B, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Arbitration (Various), 1950-1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Communication, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Disciplinary Procedure Manual, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  (Draft)
- Grievance Arbitration Procedure, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Employees' Appearance in the Workplace, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Arbitration and Federal Rights Under Collective Agreements in '71 and '72, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Public Employees Labor Relations NYC-NYS, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- ILR Reprint Series 184 and 225 + Issues in Industrial Society, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Public Employee Labor Relations (General), 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Protection Labor Laws (U.S.U), 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Protective Labor Laws- NY State Workmen's Corporation- Employment Insurance, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Personal Management, 1954-1962 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- N.L. R.B, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Management Rights ---- Course announcements. (Box 10)
  - Management R Shts., 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - FMES FEN-SZNVICE ARB, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Legal Developments, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Federal, 1973-1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.356, 1962-1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 550 To Be Weard, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Course Announcements (Not LY), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Bus. Services ---- Foreign Labor Relations. (Box 11)
  - Bus Sources, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - ILR Literature, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration- Law, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Process, 1951-1954 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Industrial Psychology, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - British Labor Rel, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Labor Relations, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 8)